Kristen Killingsworth

316-350-4963 Killingsworth kristen@yahoo.com

Summary

I am a hard worker with experience that is transferrable to many fields and jobs. I am an incredibly strong writer and have experience with social media marketing. Additionally, I am a very friendly person who is perfect for teamwork as well as maintaining professional business relationships.

Education

BACHELOR OF THE ARTS | DECEMBER 2020 | UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON

- · Major: Culture, Literature, and the Arts
- · Minor: Gender, Women, and Sexuality Studies
- · Related coursework:
 - o Global Cultural Studies
 - 10 hours of volunteer work at the Burke National history museum (received basic collections/object handling training). Built mounts for objects in the SE Asian collection.
 - o Histories and Movements of Gender and Sexuality
 - Conducted feminist research on Local organization Skillspire. Experienced with conducting interviews and transcribing them. Link to archive: <a href="https://cdm16786.contentdm.oclc.org/digital/collection/p16786coll12/search/searc

Experience

REGISTERED BEHAVIOR TECHNICIAN | ATTAIN ABA | JANUARY 2022-PRESENT

· Working with children with autism to teach them skills (functional communication, problem behavior reduction, etc.) Received RBT certification from the BACB.

ENGLISH INSTRUCTOR | (EMPLOYED BY) BEST IN CLASS EDUCATION | JANUARY 2019-MARCH 2020

· Highly proficient at multi-tasking to be able to teach 6 children at one time and excellent grasp of English grammar and writing

MANAGER | EDIBLE ARRANGEMENTS | JANUARY 2015-OCTOBER 2018

- · Managed payroll, scheduling, hiring/firing/discipline
- · Maintained professional social media accounts and cultivated local business partnerships
- Being flexible to take on any role (i.e. delivery, making arrangements, customer service, cleaning, etc.)